

Hi, I'm Olivia! I am a junior at Parsons School of Design studying a BFA in Communication Design. I have a background in graphic design, website design, branding, and illustration. I'm interested in creating unique experiences through technology and interaction.









## **SKILLS**

Photoshop Creative InDesign Organized Illustrator Collaboration Premiere Pro Typography Social Media Website Design HTML & CSS UI/UX Figma Branding Google Suite Illustration Microsoft Office Photography

## **EDUCATION**

Parsons School of Design, The New School August 2020-present

Communication Design BFA (GPA: 3.9)

CS50: Introduction to Computer Science June 2020–August 2020

Harvard edX Online Course

Sharron Art Center June 2020-August 2020

Refined my fundamental art skills through sketching, painting, and sculpture.

## **LANGUAGES**

English
Chinese
Spanish
•••••••

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Yeh IDeology & Thrive By Design | Creative Intern May 2022-August 2022

Developed the layout, marketing language tone, info structure, interactions, animations, typography and color scheme of Thrive By Design's website. Created monthly newsletters with animated graphics and marketing language for Yeh IDeology.

# Youth and Sustainability | Brand & Website Designer March 2022-April 2022

Designed the logo, colors, and chose typography for brand. Coded and designed the mobile website. Collaborated with a team to develop identity and content for brand.

### **INTERESTS**





Dancing

Movies





Music

Drawing

# Portfolio Editor and Photographer | Freelance

Oct 2020-Dec 2020

Assisted multiple art students by photographing and editing their artworks for art contests and developing college art portfolios.

## **Embolden Jewelry | Branding Designer**

June 2020-August 2020

Created logos, designed graphics, photographed products, and composed layout of website/Instagram feed.

## Starbucks | Barista

July 2021-August 2021

Memorized and crafted an array of beverages in a fast-paced working environment while communicating with coworkers and customers to facilitate the best experience.



Travel Comics

## **AWARDS**

- National Medal from Scholastic Art and Writing Awards 2020
- High Merit Student Award from Celebrating Art Contest 2019 & 2020
- National Art Honor Society and Academic Honor Roll in High School